But while we are fighting every day to build up our nation,
the far left only wants to wreck ruin and destroy our nation.
And you know better than anybody.
For the last three years, Democrat lawmakers,
their deep state cronies, the fake news media,
they've been colluding in their effort to overturn
the presidential election.
63 million people voted and to nullify the votes of the American people.
And many African-American people voted for Trump.
Even then, now they like me more because I said I was going to do it,
and now I did it, so you better vote.
I said I was going to do it.
I said I'm going to do it.
Yeah?
Long live, long live, long live, long live, long live.
Thank you, folks.